# LINA LANGFORD

503 E Braidhill Dr Draper, Utah • 801-258-1184 • lina.langford235@gmail.com

### **SUMMARY**

Creative and analytical professional with multiple years' experience in back-end operations environment. Knowledge in multiple coding languages, leading design software, and great communication skills. Highly-motivated and enthusiastic team player with excellent problem solving skills and dedicated to efficiently resolving project issues and meeting strict deadlines.

# **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- 2+ years' experience in HealthEquity's Console system
- Adobe Suite Collection (Photoshop, Illustrator, Light room, InDesign etc.)
- Visual Studios
- Excel, Microsoft Word, and PowerPoint
- Technical writing experience

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

HealthEquity, Draper, UT

June, 2017 to Present

## Position: Web Development Intern

- Design and create new mock-up website designs involving heavy amounts of UX & UI design
- Translate designs into code
- Responsible for updating current company learning sites and debugging web pages

# HealthEquity, Draper, UT

September, 2016 to May, 2017

#### Position: Bulk Transfer Coordinator

- Heavy amounts of project management on a day to day basis
- Executed transactions dealing with bulk transfers through Console
- Organized all project details of bulk transfers coming into HealthEquity and going out
- Designed bulk transfer resources and built foundation for process

# HealthEquity, Draper, UT

Oct., 2014 to Sep., 2016

# Position: Operations Supervisor (Check Processing & Inbound Ops)

- Managed multiple teams in Ops providing training in Console, daily team transactional tasks, and meeting strict team deadlines
- Daily problem solving operational transactions through Console
- Balanced financial records, provided quality assurance
- Created and approved over 20 technical writing procedures

# Abeo Corporation, Sandy, UT

August, 2011 to July, 2014

### Position: Customer Service Supervisor

Tasks include hiring, training, and managing team of 15 individuals on customer service & collections

### **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Science Degree – Web Development & Design		University of Utah, UT School of Engineering
References		
Kristi Gardner	HealthEquity Operations Director	Phone: 801.727.1157
<ul> <li>Cassie Blake</li> </ul>	HealthEquity Operations Manager	Phone: 801-727-1020
<ul> <li>Kathleen Burr</li> </ul>	HealthEquity AM Group Leader	Phone: 801-727-1123